[{"id": 3069, "question": "Ladji Doucoure of France beat Olympic champion Liu Xiang of China in the final meters to claim the title of the men's 110 meters hurdles at the 10thworld championships in Helsinki on Friday. Doucoure, who led the world this season with 12.97 seconds, over took the Chinese to win the race in 13.07 seconds. Liu was second in 13.08. Four-time world champion Allen Johnson of the United States took the third in 13.10. The 22-year-old Doucoure said after the race, \" I can not tell you just how long I have been dreaming of this. This victory is the result of a lot of hard work, and also a lot of support from people who have believed in me. I had a bad start, touched a few hurdles, but after the 4thhurdle I _ and went straight to the finish line.\" Liu, who won the Olympic gold with a world record-...\n\nQ: This passage probably appears  _  .", "options": ["in a story book", "in a text book", "in a newspaper", "in a fashion magazine"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2195, "question": "Trans-Bridge Tours is looking forward to providing you with another year of exciting One-Day travel destinations in 2016. Statue of Liberty & Ellis Island August 15 (Sat) $78 Adult; $66 Child (4-12); $ 75 Senior (62+) No visit to the New York City area is complete without a trip to the world's most famous landmarks--- the Statue of Liberty and Ellis Island. Price includes transportation to Liberty State Park and timed ferry tickets. 9/11 Museum& Memorial September 29 (Tue) $ 87 Adult; $ 78 Youth (7-17); Senior $80(65+) The Museum displays artifacts associated with the events of 9/11, while presenting stories of loss and recovery. The Memorial between the twin reflecting pools, is a tribute of remembrance and honor to the nearly 3,000 people killed in the terror attacks. The New York Botani...\n\nQ: Which was set up in memory of the victims of the terrorist attacks?", "options": ["The Statue of Liberty.", "The 9/11 Memorial.", "Hagley Museum.", "Winterthur Garden."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3287, "question": "From a very early age, some children show better self-control than others. Now, a new study that began with about 1,000 children in New Zealand has tracked how a child's low self-control can predict poor health, money troubles and even a criminal record in their adult years. Researchers have been studying this group of children for decades now. They observed the level of self-control the youngsters displayed. Parents, teachers, even the kids themselves, scored the youngsters on measures like \"acting before thinking\" and \"Persistence in reaching goals.\" The study led by Moffitt of Duke University and colleagues followed 1,000 children from birth to age 32 in Dunedin, New Zealand. \"The children who had the lowest self-control when they were age three to ten, later on had the most health prob...\n\nQ: Children with low self-control are more likely to_.", "options": ["become wealthy in later life", "get good school performance", "have better financial planning", "adopt negative behaviors"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2123, "question": "The worst days of any summer are the rainy ones. We spend all year looking forward to nice weather and long, hot days. In winter, with its cloudy days and bitter cold, we dream of those days at the beach, lying on the sand and enjoying the bright and burning sun. And then, summer comes, and it rains. As a child, I would wake up to rainy summer days and come close to crying. It wasn't fair. We suffered through months of school and experienced bad weather for those short ten weeks of freedom. On those rainy summer days, I had nothing fun to do and could only sit inside, staring out at the rain like a bird in a cage. I was an only child, so there was no one else to play with. My father worked from home, so I was not truly alone, but he could not actively play with me since he was at work. It ...\n\nQ: As an adult, the author views summer rain differently because   _  .", "options": ["rain makes the weather cooler", "his summer holiday is very short", "he knows it won't last long", "he can better deal with his spare time"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2284, "question": "Where can you find a nice place to relax on holiday for both you and your children? Well, I suggest you try the beautiful and green Isle of Wight (IOW). The Isle of Wight is one of the main tourist attractions. Here is some information on a few of the attractions on the IOW. Dinosaur Isle It is located in Sandown, a seaside town on the southeast coast. It's a large, lovely museum, both fun and educational. Here you can see a large fossil collection of all kinds of dinosaurs, as well as a gift shop. You can walk into the past and then the future, learning about the history and the development of the civilization of dinosaurs that lived 120 million years ago. Robin Hill Country Park The park is in the beautiful countryside, and is suitable for children's parties and games. It has five new ga...\n\nQ: You can read this article in a   _  .", "options": ["travel magazine", "science journal", "book review", "film advertisement"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2633, "question": "Beijing (Xinhua) -- In 2010, some 108,000 people returned to the Chinese mainland from abroad, a number that had risen 56.2 percent from the previous year, according to statistics recently published by the Ministry of Education. \"For Chinese employers, a 70 percent willingness to hire overseas workers, although that is still lower than the average rate of 76 percent for Asia, is quite a high figure when compared with the past,\" said Emma, regional director of Hays in Hong Kong and the mainland, who was in charge of the survey . Company executives , she said, have recently come to prefer hiring Chinese natives who have returned home after studying or working elsewhere.Expatriates have fallen to a second choice, she said. In the past, expatriates and returned Chinese have earned three to fou...\n\nQ: What can be inferred from this news report?", "options": ["Employers without overseas experiences are gaining increasing equality.", "Overseas candidates have received better education and training.", "Chinese employers have a prejudice against native employees.", "Overseas candidates still have better chances to rise to executives."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 802, "question": "Studies show that you may be lied to every day anywhere from 10 to 200 times. We say, \"Nice song.\" \"Honey, you don't look fat in that, no.\" But another study showed that strangers lied three times within the first 10 minutes of meeting each other. We lie more to strangers than we lie to coworkers. Men lie eight times more about themselves than they do other people. Women lie more to protect other people. If you're married, you're going to lie to your wife/ husband in one out of every 10 communications. If you're unmarried, that number drops to three. But look, if at some point you got lied to, it's because you agreed to get lied to. Truth about lying: lying's a cooperative act. Not all lies are harmful. Sometimes we're willing to lie for the sake of social dignity , maybe to keep a private...\n\nQ: From Para.1 we learn that lying is very   _  .", "options": ["harmful", "easy", "interesting", "common"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2450, "question": "Today, Mount Qomolangma's peak is not a lonely place any more. More than 3,500 people have successfully climbed the 8,844m mountain, and more than a tenth of that number reached the peak just over the past year. As more and more people try to test themselves against Qomolangma, many a time the mount can be very crowded. Climbers have complained about waiting for hours in the bottlenecks on the way to the peak. If bad weather strikes, climbers can and do die. But the dangerous crowds aren't the only problem on Qomolangma. All those climbers need to bring a lot of _ --much of them ends up being left on the mountain, sometimes even the peak itself. Mount Qomolangma is becoming the world's tallest rubbish dump. Here's mountaineer Mark Jenkins writing in National Geographic about the state of Q...\n\nQ: The group of 15 Nepali artists   _  .", "options": ["created works of art using rubbish from Qomolangma", "were employed by the Everest Peakeers Association", "climbed Qomolangma and collected 1.5 tons of trash", "painted 74 beautiful pictures of Mount Qomolangma's peak"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3185, "question": "What I like to advise people is to find out what it is that makes them happy. What do you love to do? If you truly love what you do just go ahead and try to make a living by doing it. People will throw money at you to do it. But you will always have to work hard at it. I have to draw every single day of my life. I have to draw about 20 ideas. My advice is to put aside a certain amount of time every day and make you draw or whatever, especially when you don't feel like it. Only in this way will you be able to perfect your talent. The first step you take is to go to your local library and ask for the publications issued in the current years. When you get these publications, try to find the names of the top people concerned and their presidents. After you find these, write down their names an...\n\nQ: The purpose of writing a letter to the president was to   _  .", "options": ["get some money to support the later career", "enclose the information on how to become cartoonists with the letter", "focus his attention on the work", "explain who would be the readers of the work"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 976, "question": "Schouten University is a highly respected online education provider offering officially-recognized degree programs across the globe. Our mission is to provide students with a high-quality mixed learning MBA program and personal coaching to help them to become world-class managers. MBA with Unique Skills & Personal Development Program Students will benefit from 30 years of soft skills training experience from Schouten & Nielsen, the leading soft skills training institute in Europe. To become an effective manager, theory alone is not enough, and being able to put theory into practice is more important today than ever before. With the Schouten University MBA program you will have the unique opportunity to develop such soft skills as influencing skills, leadership skills, communication skills ...\n\nQ: According to the advertisement, which of the following DOESN'T belong to soft skills?", "options": ["Leadership skills.", "Communication skills.", "Driving skills.", "Motivational skills."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1110, "question": "Joke l: A man was sitting reading his papers when his wife hit him round the head with a frying pan. \"What was that for?\" the man asked. The wife replied, \"That was for the piece of paper with the name Jenny on it I found in your pocket.\" The man then said, \"When l was at the races last week Jenny was the name of the horse I bet on.\" The wife apologized and went on with the housework. Three days later the man was watching TV when his wife hit him on the head with an even bigger frying pan, knocking him unconscious. Upon regaining consciousness the man asked why she had hit again. Wife replied, \"Your horse phoned.\" Joke 2: \"Do you believe in life after death?\" the boss asked one of his employees. \"Yes, sir, \" the new employee replied. \"Well, then, that makes everything just fine, \" the boss...\n\nQ: What dose the boss mean in Joke 2?", "options": ["He was lucky to see the employee's former grandmother.", "The employee's grandmother has come into heaven after death.", "He has figured out that the employee told a lie to him.", "The employee's grandmother was an honest woman."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1476, "question": "If you're a man and you're reading this, congratulations: you're a survivor. According to statistics, you're more than twice as likely to die of skin cancer than a woman, and nine times more likely to die of AIDS. Even if you make it to the end of your natural term, about 78 years for men in Australia, you'll die on average five years before a woman. There're many reasons for this--typically, men take more risks than women and are more likely to drink and smoke--but perhaps more importantly, men don't go to the doctor. \"Men aren't seeing doctors as often as they should,\" says Dr. Gullotta. \"This is particularly so for the over-40s, when chances of diseases are higher .\" Gullotta says a healthy man should visit the doctor every year or two. For those over 45, it should be at least once a ye...\n\nQ: What is Cartmill's opinion of regular check-ups for men?", "options": ["They may increase public expenses.", "They will save money in the long run.", "They may cause trouble for men.", "They will enable men to live as long as women."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2882, "question": "On the way home from school, Jack always passes a park. His mother said it was dangerous to pass by the park at night, but it is the fastest way home. Today, after finishing soccer practice, Jack was walking toward the park as usual. Suddenly, Jack heard someone calling him, \"Excuse me!\" Jack turned around, and there was an old woman. \"Yes, ma'am.\" Jack answered politely. \"Don't pass by the park tonight.\" Her voice was weak and dry. \"Okay, ma'am,\" said Jack carelessly. The old woman held Jack's hand strongly, and said, \"I mean it!\" Jack felt the hairs on his neck stand up. As soon as the lady let go of his hand, he started to run. This time, he ran so fast that he didn't have time to think where he was going. When he stopped, he realized he was in the middle of the park. He remembered what...\n\nQ: Who might be the person that screamed?", "options": ["Jack himself.", "Jack's mother.", "Park guard.", "An actress."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1974, "question": "We found out that Jenny was suffering hearing loss when she was four and a half years old. Several operations and speech classes later, when she was seven, we found out that Jenny had Juvenile Rheumatoid Arthritis . She could not put pressure on the heels of her feet, so she walked on tiptoe , and when the pain became unbearable, I carried her. Jenny was fortunate, though, because she did not suffer the deformities , often associated with JRA. All through grade school, and on into high school, Jenny suffered, yet never complained. She took her medicine, and I would often wrap her feet in steaming towels, and hold her until the pain eased. But, as soon as she could stand the pain, Jenny, immediately, carried on, as though she were pain-free. She wore a smile on her face, a song on her lips,...\n\nQ: According to the passage, Jenny was mainly described as  _  .", "options": ["a professional football player", "a different kind of athlete", "a disabled athlete full of ambitions", "A disabled girl full of ideas"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1283, "question": "When looking for love, people may go to some extreme lengths. They might go on blind dates set up by family and friends. They might write personal ad to place in newspapers. Or they might use a computer to help them in their search for a soul mate by joining an online dating service. Some people have even tried to find their perfect match through game shows on television. Many of these TV dating shows, including The Bachelor andWho Wants to Marry Multimillionaire?, have proved to be popular, with millions of viewers watching each week to find out which of the contestants will find true love. Of all these game shows, perhaps the one with the most unexpected ending was Mr. Right, which was shown in England in 2002. On the show, a bachelor, thirty-five-year-old Lance Gerrard-Wright, dated fif...\n\nQ: Which of the following did NOT happen during the series?", "options": ["Lance went on dates with several women.", "Lance took the women to some very good restaurants.", "Lance and Ulrika started dating each other.", "The women met Lance's family."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1715, "question": "Healthy relationships are fun and make you feel good about yourself. The relationships that you make in your teenage years will be a special pan of your life. They will teach you some of the most important lessons about who you are. This may help you understand different kinds of relationships, what makes each relationship special, and how to communicate in a positive way. What makes a relationship healthy? Communication and Sharing: The most important part of any healthy relationship between two people is being able to talk and listen to each other. You and the other person can find out what your common interests are. You can share your feelings with the other person and trust that he or she will be there to listen to you and support you. In healthy relationships, people don't lie. Commun...\n\nQ: When disagreements happen, you learn to stay calm because   _  .", "options": ["talking calmly helps you to understand the real reason for not getting along", "talking calmly makes it much easier to figure out how to fix them", "working through disagreements often makes the relationship stronger", "all of the above"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1442, "question": "Onceupon a time there was a wise man that used to go to the sea to do his writing. Hehad a habit of walking on the beach before he began his work.One day he waswalking along the shore. As he looked down at the beach, he saw a human figuremoving like a dancer. He smiled to himself at the thought that someone woulddance on the beach. So he began to walk faster to catch up. As he got closer, hesaw that it was a young man and the young man wasn't dancing, but instead he wasreaching down to the shore, picking up something and throwing itinto the ocean. As he got closer, he called out, \"Good morning! What are youdoing?'' Theyoung man paused, looked up and replied, \"Throwingstarfishes in theocean.\" \"I guess I should have asked, why are you throwing starfishes in the ocean?\" \"The sun is up and the...\n\nQ: One day, the wise man saw a young man   _  .", "options": ["dancing along the beach", "walking with a dancer", "picking up starfish for sale", "trying to save as many starfishes as possible"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 933, "question": "Talk about a real-life hero! Ten-year-old Larry Champagne from St. Louis, Missouri, hit the brake on a runaway school bus. He saved himself and 20 other kids on board from disaster. It all happened in one terrible accident. On the way to school, the bus driver, Ernestine Blackman, suddenly fell ill. Seeing the car was running away, the other kids started to scream, but Larry ran to the front and stopped the bus. \"At first I thought, 'We're going to die,'\" says Larry, \"but after I pressed the brake, I felt safe.\" Larry's speedy reaction made news all over the country. He appeared on TV shows as a hero. The bus company gave Larry a big gift. His school hung a medal of honor around his neck. \"My grandmother always tells me to do what's right,\" says Larry. He thanked his brother, Jerrick, 9, w...\n\nQ: Larry got the following as praise for his hero action Except   _  .", "options": ["appearing on TV shows", "a scholarship from his school", "a big gift from the bus company", "a medal of honor"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2395, "question": "There's a guy like me in every state and federal prison in America,I guess--I'm the guy who can get these for you:cigarettes,a bag of cigar,if you want that,a bottle of wine to celebrate your son or daughter's high school graduation,or almost anything else...within reason,that is.It wasn't always that way. I came to Shawshank when I was just twenty,and I am one of the few people in the prison who is willing to admit what he did.I committed murder.I put a large insurance policy on my wife,who was three years older than 1 was,and then I fixed the brakes of the car her father had given us as a wedding present.It worked out exactly as I had planned,except I hadn't planned on her stopping to pick up the neighbour woman and the woman's son on the way down Castle Hill and into town.The brakes let...\n\nQ: By saying that\"I got a pass into this place\"(in Para.3),the man means that  _  .", "options": ["he has got to stay in prison", "he was allowed to go home", "he was caught by the police without a pass", "he has stayed in the federal prison before"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1788, "question": "Here is some must-know information from a handbook on how people behave in doing business in some countries. In Brazil Brazilians are warm and friendly.They often stand close when talking and it is common for them to touch the person on the shoulder.People often greet each other (particularly women)with light cheek kisses . Schedules tend to be flexible,with business meetings sometimes starting later than planned.But to be safe,be on time.Meals can stretch for hours--there's no such thing as rushing a meal in Brazil.Lunches also can start in the mid to late afternoon.Brazilians are social,preferring face-to-face communication over emails or phone calls. In Singapore Singaporeans shake hands when they meet and often also greet each other with a small,polite bow.Business cards should be offe...\n\nQ: In which country do people care about where to put their hands at the dinner table?", "options": ["In Brazil.", "In Singapore.", "In the United Arab Emirate.", "In Switzerland."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 61, "question": "Nelson Mandela was a figure of international fame, and many details of his life and career were public knowledge. But here are four things you may not have known about the late South African leader. 1. He was a boxing fan. In his youth, Nelson Mandela enjoyed boxing and long-distance running. Even during the 27 years he spent in prison, he would exercise every morning. \"I did not enjoy the violence of boxing so much as the science of it. I was curious by how one moved one's body to protect oneself, how one used a strategy both to attack and retreat, how one paced oneself over a match,\" he wrote in his autobiography Long Walk to Freedom. 2. His original name was not Nelson. Rolihlahla Mandela was nine years old when a teacher at the primary Methodist school where he was studying in Qunu, So...\n\nQ: Why did Nelson Mandela love boxing?", "options": ["Because he wanted to be a boxer.", "Because he enjoyed the violence of boxing.", "Because he appreciated the strategy in boxing.", "Because he had nothing else to do in the prison."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 409, "question": "I was brought up in the British, _ . Strong feelings aren't something you display in public. So, you can imagine that I was unprepared for the outpouring of public grief at a Chinese funeral. My editorial team leader died recently after a short illness. He was 31. The news was so unexpected that it left us all shocked and upset. A female colleague burst into tears and cried piteously at her desk. Somehow we got through the day's work. The next day was the funeral. Our big boss stepped forward to deliver a eulogy and was soon in tears. She carried on, in Chinese of course, but at the end said in English: \"There will be no more deadlines for you in heaven.\" Next came a long-term colleague who also dissolved in tears but carried on with her speech despite being almost overcome by emotion. The...\n\nQ: It is implied that  _  .", "options": ["the English might cry noisily for the dead in Dickens' time", "Chinese express their sadness quite unlike other peoples", "victims of terrorist bombings should be greatly honored", "English funeral culture is more civilized than the others"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 731, "question": "The adder is the only poisonous snake native to Britain. Adders have the most highly developed poison injecting mechanism of all snakes, but they are not aggressive animals. Adders will only use their poison as a last means of defence, usually if caught or trodden on. No one has died from adder bites in Britain for over 20 years. By faar the most common smake in Britain is the adder. In Scotland, in fact, there are no other snakes at all. The adder is also the only British sanke with a poisonous bite. It can be found almost anywhere, but prefers sunny hillsides and rough open country, including high gournd. In Ireland there are no snakes at all. Most people regard snake bites as a fatal misfortune, but not all bites are serious, and very few are fatal . Sometimes attempts at emergency trea...\n\nQ: What's the best title of the passage?", "options": ["Poisonous Snakes", "Adders in Britain", "Take Care oif Sake Bites", "Protec Endangered Adders"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2850, "question": "Daniel Brown was just five years old when he climbed into the family car and let it roll away down the road. He was only three when he flooded the kitchen. His mother, Angela Brown is very busy looking after her new baby, a little girl called Laura, as well as Daniel. She told us, \"Daniel is so full of curiosity .\" At that moment, we hear a loud noise and then silence. We go upstairs and find Daniel getting out of a wardrobe which he has pulled over onto the floor, with a book in his hand. \"It's for you, Mum,\" he says and looks up at his mum and smiles. Seven-year-old Daniel has a lovely face. He has golden hair, big brown eyes, and a friendly smile. I have to admit that Daniel doesn't look like a naughty boy. Angela told me all about it, \"Once I found him as he was about to put Jasper in ...\n\nQ: Which of the following is TRUE?", "options": ["Laura, as well as Daniel, is full of curiosity about everything.", "Daniel is naughty, but he is the cleverest student in his school.", "The mother thinks Daniel's curiosity leads to his naughtiness.", "Laura will be as naughty as her brother when she grows up."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3255, "question": "Teachers and textbooks _ -- your future could be under threat from a quickly developing and very smart technology. University of California researchers led by Jacob White hill recently programmed teaching robots to react to facial expression. Whitehill's achievement marked a major step forward in the way people could one day learn by establishing facial expression recognition in robot teachers. The teaching robots or, Intelligent Tutoring Systems (ITS) are computer systems that provide personalized instruction and feedback to students without human intervention. The facial expression recognition allows a computer to react according to expressions a user makes. He said that the system was an important development in improving learning systems. \"Classical ITS typically have a somewhat rigid ...\n\nQ: According to the text, we can infer that", "options": ["in the future, students will not need textbooks at all", "the developed ITS can answer any question students ask", "facial expression recognition in ITS has existed for a long time", "in the future teaching robots will possibly take the place of human teachers"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 334, "question": "Water is very important to living things. Without water there can be no life on the earth. All animals and plants need water. Man also needs water. We need water to drink, to cook our food and to clean ourselves. Water is needed in offices, factories and schools. Water is needed everywhere. There is water in seas, rivers and lakes. Water is found almost everywhere. Even in the desert part of the world, there is some water in the air. You can not see or feel it when it is a part of the air. The water in the seas, rivers and lakes is a liquid, the water in the air is a gas, and we call it water vapour . Clouds are made of water. They may be made of very small drops of water. They may also be made of snow crystals . Snow crystals are very very small crystals of ice. Ice is frozen water. It is...\n\nQ: Where can we find water?", "options": ["We can find water when it turns into vapour.", "Water is only in seas and rivers.", "We can see water in deserts here and there.", "Water can be found almost everywhere."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3013, "question": "We might not be alone in the universe. Actually, it may be confirmed as a very crowded place by new computer models developed to help identify habitable planets. Estimates of places where life can exist have been based on the possibility of them having surface water. But software recently developed by the Aberdeen University allows researchers to identify planets with underground water kept liquid by heat from planets. Water is fundamental for life and planets too close to the sun lose water to the atmosphere through evaporation. On the other hand, planets located in distant reaches from their star have their surface water locked away as ice. Sean McMahon, who is carrying out the work, explained: \"Traditionally people have said that if a planet is in this Goldilocks zone--not too hot and n...\n\nQ: What is considered as the symbol of life existence traditionally?", "options": ["Solid water on its surface.", "Solid water below ground.", "Liquid water below ground.", "Liquid water on its surface."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1268, "question": "The International Voluntary Service runs a number of Youth Exchanges throughout the year.Youth Exchanges give small groups of 4-5 young people the opportunity to take part in volunteering trips abroad for an average of two weeks.These young people are joined by 4-5 young people from 3-4 other nationalities and are a wonderful intercultural experience in a safe environment. Example Youth Exchanges: Youth Exchange 1 Location:Ireland Other nationalities:Ireland,Spain,Italy,Hungary Theme:Focuses on the topic of community reconstruction and community activities--exploring how local issues facing our communities are connected to global issues.The group will also learn about the eco-village as an example of a community and take part in team-building activities. Youth Exchange 2 Location:France Ot...\n\nQ: If you are interested in protecting the environment,you can take part in  _  .", "options": ["Youth Exchange 1", "Youth Exchange 2", "Youth Exchange 3", "Youth Exchange 4"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 978, "question": "Schouten University is a highly respected online education provider offering officially-recognized degree programs across the globe. Our mission is to provide students with a high-quality mixed learning MBA program and personal coaching to help them to become world-class managers. MBA with Unique Skills & Personal Development Program Students will benefit from 30 years of soft skills training experience from Schouten & Nielsen, the leading soft skills training institute in Europe. To become an effective manager, theory alone is not enough, and being able to put theory into practice is more important today than ever before. With the Schouten University MBA program you will have the unique opportunity to develop such soft skills as influencing skills, leadership skills, communication skills ...\n\nQ: If you attend the two Residential Study weeks, you will have to pay for   _   besides your tuition.", "options": ["housing", "participation fees", "meals", "travel costs"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 363, "question": "Throughout the world, clothing has many uses. It is used to provide protection from cold. It is also worn to prevent others from seeing specific parts of one's body. However, the parts of the body that must be covered vary widely throughout the world. Some clothing is worn to provide supernatural protection. Wearing a lucky shirt to take an exam is calling for supernatural assistance. People in all cultures use clothing and other forms of bodily decoration to communicate status , intentions and other messages. In North America, we dress differently for business and various leisure activities. North American women usually are much more knowledgeable of little difference in messages communicated by clothes than men. At times, this leads to silly mistakes of understanding of female intentions...\n\nQ: Which of the following is the best title for this passage?", "options": ["Clothing and Culture", "Ways of Sending Message", "Clothing and Social Behavior", "Communication through Clothing"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 710, "question": "Children grow quickly, especially their feet, but many families cannot buy new shoes each time a child needs them. As a result, about 300 million children around the world go barefoot. Those children risk picking up diseases and parasites from the soil. An American man may have a solution for those barefoot kids -- a shoe that grows with the child. Kenton Lee is the creator of The Shoe That Grows. He explains how the shoe works and how it is able to last so long. \"It grows in three places: the front; it can also grow on the side with Velcro; and on the back with our buckle. It can last up to five years. The bottom is compressed rubber like tire rubber. The top is just high-quality leather.\" The shoe comes in two sizes: small that fits children aged 4 to 9 and large for children aged 9 to 1...\n\nQ: Why does Kenton Lee keep a pair of his own shoes in the office?", "options": ["To remind him of his promise.", "To copy the design of them.", "To get a change conveniently.", "To use them as an example."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1643, "question": "NEW ORLEANS --A two-story, 1,500-ton and 16,000-square foot school built in 1879 is being moved about 300 yards to make way for the new University Medical Center in MidCity. The school' s relocation is marked as the largest structure ever to be moved in Louisiana and one of the top-ten heaviest in America.Officials originally had planned to _ the McDonogh No.11 School, but agreed to move the historic building at the city's request. The school is being moved on a platform of steel beams put under the schoolhouse floor, then set on 38 remote-controlled power dollies made mobile by 300 tires.The school is creeping forward on a short stay that will take about two days to move it about 300 yards. State officials said the operation shows how closely the state and city leaders are working toprese...\n\nQ: The purpose of the school relocation is   _  .", "options": ["to show the generosity of the city government", "to form a bigger education company", "to leave room for a new project", "to build a new museum for education"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1566, "question": "Sports, drama, and a variety of organizations keep students busy during high school. Where do they find the money to do these things? Not everyone gets it from Mommy and Daddy. Most have to pay for these activities. Some adults question if high school students should have jobs. Some people worry that teens with after-school jobs will struggle to find time for homework. Actually, the responsibility of having a job helps teens prioritize their time. Many jobs take only a couple of hour shifts on weeknights. According to a survey, 86 percent of high school students have an after-school, weekend or summer job and students who work between 10 and 20 hours per week during the school year have statistically higher grades-point averages than those who do not work at all. Those who work in high sch...\n\nQ: Who does the author worry about most?", "options": ["Teens who have trouble in balancing their study and work", "Teens who will face much stress when working part-time.", "Teens who have to learn to take responsibility for themselves.", "Teens who have to be independent without any work experience."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1364, "question": "Tom appeared on the sidewalk with a bucket of whitewash and a long-handled brush. He stopped by the fence in front of the house where he lived with his aunt Polly. He looked at it, and all joy left him. The fence was long and high. He put the brush into the whitewash and moved it along the top of the fence. He repeated the operation. He felt he could not continue and sat down. He knew that his friends would arrive soon with all kinds of interesting plans for the day. They would walk past him and laugh. They would make jokes about his having to work on a beautiful summer Saturday. The thought burned him like fire. He put his hand into his pockets and took out all that he owned. Perhaps he could find some way to pay someone to do the whitewashing for him. But there was nothing of value in hi...\n\nQ: Why did Tom take all his bits of toys out of his pockets?", "options": ["Because he is tired and wanted to play with his toys.", "Because he wanted to throw his toys away.", "Because he wanted to know if he could buy help with his toys.", "Because he wanted to give his toys to his friends."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 517, "question": "In 2005,the American artist Richard Prince's photograph of a photograph,Untitled(Cowboy),was sold for $1 248 000. Prince is certainly not the only contemporary artist to have worked with so-called \"found photographs\"--a loose term given to everything from discarded prints discovered in a junk shop to old advertisements or amateur photographs from a stranger's family album.The German artist Joachim Schmid,who believes \"basically everything is worth looking at\",has gathered discarded photographs,postcards and newspaper images since 1982.In his on-going project,Archiv,he groups photographs of family life according to themes:people with dogs;teams;new cars;dinner with the family;and so on. Like Schmid,the editors of several self-published art magazines also champion found photographs.One of th...\n\nQ: The author's attitude toward found photographs can be described as  _  .", "options": ["critical", "doubtful", "optimistic", "satisfied"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2445, "question": "It's not easy to find a person with the qualities it takes to be a hero. I didn't really understand the meaning of the word \"hero\" until my third year in the college. If you saw her, you wouldn't think she really looks the part, but she is stronger than Superman could ever be. Her name is Sandra Keierleber. I first met her at volleyball tryouts , but didn't notice anything special at first. As the week passed, however, she showed she had more heart than anyone. She stood out because she never gave up, no matter what. Sandra isn't the tallest or the fastest --- in fact, this was her first time playing volleyball and it showed--- but that didn't stop her. She was always the first to arrive and the last to leave. By the end of tryouts she had found a place in everyone's heart. When the name l...\n\nQ: Which of the following is true about Sandra?", "options": ["She was born a volleyball player.", "She is popular with her teammates", "She does things in an easy way.", "She isn't the tallest but the fastest."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2198, "question": "Medicine comes in lots of different packages. Painkillers in a tablet can make your headache go away. Antibiotic cream from a tube can prevent your cuts from becoming infected. But can medicine come packaged in chicken eggs? A team of scientists from Scotland say \"yes\". They've engineered special chickens that lay eggs with disease-treating drugs inside. These eggs come from chickens that have been engineered to produce certain drugs inside their egg whites. These drugs are made of molecules called proteins . Animals make thousands of proteins -- they're the main element in skin, hair, milk and meat. Since animals can make proteins easily, they're good candidates for making protein drugs. Researchers have already made cows, sheep and goats produce protein drugs in their milk. But chickens ...\n\nQ: The drugs in special chicken eggs can   _  .", "options": ["treat lung cancer", "help reduce headache", "change people's DNA", "treat multiple sclerosis"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1115, "question": "If you wish to dance with a certain lady, go to her, bow, and say, \"May I have the pleasure of a dance?\" If it is a formal dance with programs, she will tell you which dance she will have with you; if there are no programs, she will either rise and dance with you, or she may say, \"I have this dance taken.\" Or she may say, \"I am sorry, I am not dancing this dance.\" This may be a polite way of saying that she does not want to dance with you, or it may be that she is tired and wants to rest; you will have to judge which is her attitude. Do not expect a lady whom you have invited to dance in advance for a dance to make any attempt to find you. It is her part to remain seated until you find her. Bow and say, \"I believe this is my dance.\" At the end of a dance, thank your partner, but do not lea...\n\nQ: At the end of the dance,  _  .", "options": ["you leave your partner and go to find your next partner", "you thank your partner and leave her", "you should introduce your partner to another gentleman", "none of the above is right"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2265, "question": "People appear to be born to calculate. The numerical skills of children develop so early that it is easy to imagine an internal clock of mathematical maturity guiding their growth. Not long after learning to walk and talk, they can set the table with impressive accuracy--one plate, one knife, one spoon, one fork for each of the five chairs. Soon they are capable of noting that they have placed five knives, spoons and forks on the table, and a bit later, that this amounts to fifteen pieces of silverware. Having thus mastered addition, some people expect that if a child were on a desert island at birth and brought back seven years later, he or she could enter a second-grade mathematics class without any serious problems of intellectual adjustment. Of course, the truth is not so simple. This ...\n\nQ: What does the passage mainly discuss?", "options": ["The development of mathematical ability in children.", "Tendency in teaching children mathematics.", "The use of calculating in child psychology.", "The basic concepts of mathematics that children must learn."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2608, "question": "More than two thirds of the world's polar bears will be wiped out by 2050,according to a shocking new study. By then,scientists say,global warming will have melted 42 percent of the Arctic sea ice. By 2100,only a very few of these important creatures will be left. The report has been produced by the US Geological Survey. The scientists have publicized their findings in the hope of influencing US Interior Secretary Dirk Kempthorne,who has been asked to put polar bears on the US endangered species list. Polar bears depend on floating sea ice as a platform for hunting seals,which are their main food. Without enough ice,polar bears would be forced to go onto the land,where they are poorly skilled hunters,and would be unlikely to adapt to the life on the land in time. Experts say few little bea...\n\nQ: Why will polar bears die out if there is not enough sea ice?", "options": ["Because polar bears can't catch enough food without ice.", "Because polar bears eat ice when they feel thirsty.", "Because polar bears will be easily found by hunters without ice.", "Because most female bears are used to giving birth under ice."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 761, "question": "We've all heard the phrase \"love is patient\", but one couple in prefix = st1 /Michigan, took this phrase to a whole new level. On Monday, February 13, Willard Mason sat down to talk about his relationship with the love he lost more than 60 years ago. Good fortune and fate recently helped the couple reunite. In 1941, Willard Mason and Llah Ost, both senior 2 students, became engaged to be married and began planning their lives together. But Willard moved away to work at Willow Run Bomber Plant, where he met and fell in love with a woman named Helvi. He broke off his long distance engagement to Llah and married Helvi in 1942. Llah later found love with someone else. Both had happy marriages and raised families. Then, in 2003, Helvi died. A year later, Willard found himself back in his hometo...\n\nQ: What caused the failure of Willard and Llah's engagement?", "options": ["Their unhappy company with each other.", "Llah's new love with someone else.", "Their being far away from each other.", "Willard's escape from his family."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2288, "question": "From their beginnings New England towns had a special democratic system of government. At a stated time all the citizens would assemble at a town meeting, where they would discuss local problems and express opinions freely. They also elected the town's officials at these gatherings and made decisions about the taxes they would pay and about other community matters. These meetings were usually held at the town hall, which was located in the central square. In the eighteenth-century town meetings, only men who owned property and who were church members actually voted, although everyone present was allowed to express their opinions. Later, all citizens were allowed to vote. Thus the town meeting became truly democratic. Town meetings are still common in New England communities. In recent year...\n\nQ: According to the passage, which of the following statements is NOT true?", "options": ["Citizens can elect the officials in the town meeting.", "In recent years, town meetings are often called by a government agency.", "People can say what they want to say at the town meeting.", "Nowadays this kind of meeting is also held on radio and television."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 733, "question": "Vampires , creatures of myth, have been around in one form or another for centuries. Terrifying but also attractive, they are as popular in the early 21st century as ever, as the current popularity of Twilight series, and its hero Edward Cullen, show. Vampires first appeared in fiction in the 1700s; in 1895 Irish novelist Bram Stoker published Dracula, introducing the world's most famous vampire. But just what is it about these drinkers of human blood that continues to fascinate us? Speaking to Eric Lewis of the Times and Transcript website, academic Deborah Wells said that vampires are \"culturally adaptive \". \"We create very different vampires to fit different times. Edward Cullen is not the same as Count Dracula,\" she said. Different as they are, Wells believes vampires are \"the perfect ...\n\nQ: According to the website Bookpages, today's vampires   _  .", "options": ["dare to give up traditional ideas", "may not think highly of parental authority", "desire money, power and sexual attraction", "are likely to be resisted by women"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1089, "question": "Coaches and parents always tell us to keep our goals in mind when we go for a competition. Carrying your goals and expectations into a competition is one of the biggest mistakes any athlete can make. This is a big game and you want to win. You want to score a hundred, defeat your competitors, or score a hat-trick of goals. When you carry your goals into the competitive ground with you, chances are great that you will leave that performance with disappointment and heartache, and nothing more! Expectations will _ Expectations will distract you from the performance and make your muscles tighten up. Want to perform to your potential when it counts the most? Then write your goals on a piece of paper before you leave for the game, match or race, and then leave that paper at home! Make a deal wit...\n\nQ: What might be the most suitable title for the passage?", "options": ["Keep your goals in mind", "Set your goals for a competition", "Forget your goals after competitions", "Leave your goals at home"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2138, "question": "Many kids don't drink enough water daily, according to a new study. The study's lead author, Erica Kenney, at first planned to look into the amount of sugary drinks kids were drinking in schools. However, during her research she found that many kids were simply not drinking enough water. Kenney and her team examined data from a group of 4,000 children, aged 6 to19, between the years of 2009 and 2012. The data was taken from the National Health and Nutrition Survey,a study on the health of children in the United States conducted each year by the Center for Disease Control and Prevention.. While looking through the survey results, she noticed that more than half of the kids who took part in the study were dehydrated . Of' that group, boys were 76% more likely than girls not to have enough wa...\n\nQ: What was Erica Kenney's purpose in doing the study?", "options": ["To study if kids drink enough water daily :", "To prove that sugary drinks are harmful to kids", "To show what kind of sugary drinks kids love.", "To find out how many sugary drinks kids drink at school."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2425, "question": "Millions of girls grow up with the hope of becoming a famous singer. Some even win local talent competitions as children, but only a few such early successes and dreams turn into reality. Jessica Andrews is one of the few whose dreams have come true. Andrews, first taste of success came at the age of 10. She won a talent competition in her home town of Huntingdon, Tennessee, singing I Will Always Love You, originally sung by Whitney Houston. Houston's version of the song appeared on The Bodyguard sound track, which happened to be the first album Andrews ever bought. Within two years, talk of Andrews had spread to Nashville and caught the attention of producer Byron Gallimore, whose credits include work with Tim McGraw, Faith Hill, and Jo Dee Messina. With Gallimore signed on to produce, An...\n\nQ: Which of the following is the best title of the passage?", "options": ["Jessica Andrews' Life", "Jessica Andrews' Dream", "Jessica Andrews' Songs", "Jessica Andrews' Success as a Singer"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2768, "question": "Hurricane reached the northeastern United States today and caused death and destruction everywhere. The killer storm carried winds of 135 miles per hour. The high winds and heavy rains created extremely dangerous waves. It is not yet known how many people died or were hurt in this storm, but it is said that the numbers will be very high. With the arrival of the tornado season, the National Weather Service is again telling people how to protect themselves from these deadly storms. The winds from tornadoes are the most violent winds on earth. They can blow up to 400 miles per hour. A _ looks like a funnel . It is also very loud. It may sound like a train coming at you. In fact, the winds from a tornado can pick up a train and throw it around. If a tornado is seen in your area, it is very imp...\n\nQ: According to the passage, a person who sees a tornado in his area had better NOT   _  .", "options": ["drive his car away as fast as possible", "go to the basement and wait under a table", "find a narrow place to hide", "stay away from windows"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 853, "question": "Most people think about donating blood. However, very few actually do it. Even the most consistent ones donate an average of just three to four times during their lifetime. Now the officials in Sweden are trying to change the trend with the help of modern-day technology. The encouragement to donate again begins shortly after the donor leaves the clinic when he/she receives a \"thank you\" text. Though that certainly helps them feel appreciated, what is even more pleasing is the text they receive each time their blood is used to help someone in need. Karolina Wiberg, manager of the Stockholm blood service, believes this small gesture not only results in repeat donors, but helps bring in new ones. _ that was started in Stockholm has received such positive feedback that it is now being rolled o...\n\nQ: What do people think of blood donation reminders?", "options": ["Disturbing.", "Memorable.", "Boring.", "Acceptable."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 542, "question": "Yueyang Tower lies in the west of Yueyang City, near the Dongting Lake. It was first built for soldiers to rest on and watch out. In the Three Kingdoms Period, Lu Su, General of Wu State, trained his soldiers here. In 716, Kaiyuan of Tang Dynasty, General Zhang Shuo was sent to defend at Yuezhou and he rebuilt it into a tower named South Tower, and then Yueyang Tower. In 1044, Song Dynasty, Teng Zijing was stationed at Baling Jun, the ancient name of Yueyang City. In the second year, he had the Yueyang Tower repaired and had poems by famous poets written on the walls of the tower. Fan Zhongyan, a great artist and poet, was invited to write the well-known poem about Yueyang Tower. In his A Panegyric of the Yueyang Tower (<<>> ), Fan writes: \"Be the first to worry about the troubles across t...\n\nQ: In Three-Kingdom Period, Yueyang Tower was used as   _  .", "options": ["a place where rich people enjoyed themselves", "the symbol of the Three Kingdoms", "a place where educated people often met", "an army-training place"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2903, "question": "Remember that goals are dreams with a timetable. Our goals are important for us to create what enriches our life. A very common attitude among people who are successful is that their success lies in their ability to provide themselves goals that are both numerous and exciting. When you think about your future,you are helping to feed a long-term goal of what you want to create. To realize your dreams,you must translate your vision into a series of actions you can take as soon as possible. You should be able to measure these results,to make sure they take you wherever you want. And this step should not be viewed lightly! Indeed,very few people set goals and concrete actions for themselves to achieve. Very few people note what they want to accomplish,and know each day whether they have indeed...\n\nQ: What is the best title for the passage?", "options": ["The Path towards Your Targets", "The Process of Making Goals", "The Power of Your Goals", "The Importance of Your Success"], "answer": 2}]